apester.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Apester

This Privacy Policy applies to Apester.com and any of its affiliated websites, applications and other digital services in connection with which this Privacy Policy is linked or posted (collectively, “Services”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that is collected offline or by any third-party websites or services that you may access through the Services.

This Privacy Policy explains how Apester Ltd. (collectively, “Apester”) collects and uses data and information that may identify or can be directly associated with an individual person (“Personal Information”). Apester respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This Privacy Policy explains Apester’s policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of any information we receive including your Personal Information (if any).

Apester provides a platform where content publishers (“Publisher”) can create, embed and share interactive content units, including but not limited to: online quizzes, questionnaires, feedback applications or other features (“Platform”), that can be distributed and offered on the content publisher’s website, application, mobile app or service (“Publisher Site”) and the end users of the Publisher Site can interact with (“End Users”). In this policy “Publisher” refers to any third party that downloads, implements or makes use of the Platform and/or the Services.  
This Privacy Policy applies both to Personal Information collected from employees of Publishers (“Publisher Employees”) and End Users (collectively with Publisher’s Employees and those accessing the Apester.com website, “User” or “Users”).

## Information Apester Collects from End Users

Apester uses the Platform and/or Services to collect information regarding End Users’ activities and operations that interact with the Platform or that interact with any content that may be available through the Platform. Such information includes IP-address, Session ID, browser type, mobile or desktop ID, referrer, user language and feedback or answers provided by the End User to any interactive content unit made available with the Platform. Such information may qualify as Personal Information in some End Users’ jurisdictions, however, we do not make any use of such data to directly identify individuals or to associate it with individuals.

## Information Apester collects from Publishers

In order to use the Platform or Services, Publishers have to enroll on Apester’s website and create an account by providing certain data, such as a user name and email-address and certain other information that may be provided from Publisher to Apester. Apester will also create a unique user ID to each Publisher. Where this data is attributable to a certain Publisher Employee, this may also qualify Personal Information that is collected by Apester.  
Information Apester collects from visitors of the Apester.com website  
When you access the Apester.com website, we may collect information from the computer or device that you use to access the Services, such as your operating system type, browser type, domain and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone in which your computer or device is located.

## How Apester Protects Information

Apester follows applicable laws and generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to Apester by implementing adequate technical and organizational protection measures, both during transmission and once Apester receives it. These measures will be continuously adjusted and updated in accordance with current industry standards. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while Apester strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect Personal Information, Apester cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## How Apester Uses Information

Where required by applicable laws, Apester will only process, use or share User’s Personal Information with third parties with User’s explicit permission or as described in this Privacy Policy. Apester will only disclose Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy or where required by law, regulation, subpoena or court order. Apester uses Personal Information to the extent necessary for internal purposes – for example, in connection with offering the Services, to help diagnose problems with Apester’s servers, to make Apester’s Services more useful, or to improve the Platform.

## Use of Publisher’s Employee Personal Information:

Apester collects, processes and uses Customer’s Employee Personal Information for purposes of administering the Services, and to improve the experience of the Apester Services.

## Use of End User’s Personal Information:

Apester may use information it collects, including Personal Information, to provide the End User with the Services and in order to provide End Users with advertising that Apester reasonably believes may be more useful or interesting to the End User. The Personal Information collected by Apester will not be connected by Apester to any other personal information collected by third parties for advertisement purposes. In addition, by analyzing all information Apester receives, including all information concerning End Users and their interaction with the Platform and content made available through the Platform, Apester may irreversibly compile aggregated statistical information across a variety of mobile applications and End Users (“Statistical Information”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be improved and tailored to customer desires. Statistical Information is anonymous and does not, in and of itself, identify any specific end user or customer of Apester. Apester may share such Statistical Information with its partners or any third party, without restriction, on commercial terms that Apester can determine in its sole discretion.  
Personal Information is not transferred or disclosed to third parties other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## Opt-Out

If End User does not wish its Personal Information to be collected, processed or shared for the above purposes, he may opt out from this use with effect for the future. For opting out, the End User can do so by sending an email to privacy@apester.com, or sending a paper letter to Apester’s Privacy Officer at the following address: Soncino 3 Tel Aviv 67216, P.O.box 57703, Israel. Facsimile copies can be sent to the following number: 153-3-6020065, however we do encourage you to reach out via email which is checked more often.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to the End User’s browser and stored on his computer or mobile device. All cookies used by Apester are persistent cookies, i.e. they will be stored on the User’s device after the browser session has expired. Any cookie will be deleted within one month after it has been placed unless configured otherwise. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but the User can change this setting so his browser either refuses all cookies or informs him when a cookie is being sent. Also, the User is free to delete any existing cookies at any time with future effect. Some features of Apester’s Services may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed.  
Cookies placed on End Users’ computers:  
Cookies placed on an End User’s computer will transmit the End User’s Personal Information as specified above to Apester for the purposes also specified above.  
Cookies placed on Publishers’ computers:  
Apester also uses cookies to help personalize Publisher’s Apester experience. These could be “persistent” cookies that may be used to help save Publisher’s settings and customizations across website visits. Also, if Publisher logs in to Apester, such a cookie will be used to recognize Publisher as a valid user so Publisher will not need to login each time using Apester.

## Online Links to Other Sites

### Links to third-party websites

Apester may link to other websites of third-parties that provide useful information/services. Any information User provides on the linked pages is provided directly to this third-party and is subject to that third-party’s provider’s privacy policy. Apester is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of Web sites to which it links. Links from Apester’s site to third parties or other sites are provided for User’s convenience. You should learn about the privacy practices of each web site before providing them with Personal Information.

### Social media websites and widgets

Apester may link to other websites of third-parties that provide useful information/services. Any information User provides on the linked pages is provided directly to this third-party and is subject to that third-party’s provider’s privacy policy. Apester is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of Web sites to which it links. Links from Apester’s site to third parties or other sites are provided for User’s convenience. You should learn about the privacy practices of each web site before providing them with Personal Information.

## Use of Apester by Children

Apester does not knowingly collect Personal Information from individuals under the age of 18. In the event you become aware that an individual under the age of 13 has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately.

## Other Uses or Transfer of User’s Information

Apester will disclose any information, including Personal Information, to the extent required by applicable law. Apester will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing it to disclose the identity, behavior or digital content of any User suspected to have engaged in illegal or infringing behavior.  
Uses of Personal Information described in this Privacy Policy may be accomplished by Apester or its service providers. In providing the Platform and Services, Apester may use subcontractors or service providers that are located in countries other than User’s own, including countries that might be outside the European Economic Area, and transfer to them Personal Information Apester collects and processes as further specified in here.  
Apester currently uses Google Cloud Services as a cloud and storage service provider with servers in the US, and where information obtained from the Platform or Apester’s website is stored. Google Cloud’s terms and privacy policy is available at: https://cloud.google.com/terms/ and here: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/. The Cloud Services are Privacy Shield certified (information can be found here: https://cloud.google.com/security/compliance/eu-data-protection/).  
Apester uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). Google places cookies on User’s computer to analyze User’s use of the Platform and the Apester website. The information collected by the cookie is transferred to and stored on Google servers located in the US. Apester is using commercially reasonable efforts to leverage the IP-anonymization service of Google, i.e. a service offered by Google whereby a User’s IP address will be shortened before transfer to the US. After shortening the IP addresses, the collected data cannot be directly matched to a User. Google will process and use the collected information on behalf of Apester in order to analyze User’s use of the Platform and the Apester website, to compose respective reports and to provide certain other services to Apester related to the use of the Platform and the Apester website. The IP address collected by the cookie will not be collated with other Google data. User can change the settings of his browser so it refuses all cookies of third parties. Also, User is free to delete any existing cookies at any time with future effect. User can also contradict the collection and use of data by the Google cookie by installing the browser plugin available for download under the following hyperlink: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en. For further information regarding Google Analytics please see examples of Google’s terms of use (https://www.google.com/analytics/terms), data protection overview (http://www.google.com/intl/de/analytics/learn/privacy.html) and privacy policy (www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy).  
Apester may share some of the information collected via the Platform with certain trusted partners and/or technology platforms in order to present personalized advertisements to Users. In such cases, the transfer and storage practices of the information shall be governed by the policies provided by such partners and/or technology platforms.  
Apester uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that all its service providers will be subject to nondisclosure and non-use obligations and bound to process Personal Information solely as instructed by Apester in a separate Data Processing Agreement as required under applicable law. Nevertheless, some countries where Apester’s service providers are located may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in the User’s country of residence or business.  
Apester may transfer its databases containing Personal Information of Users in connection with a sale of its business or assets or any part of them that requires the use of the databases.  
Apester may transfer Personal Information to other countries whose privacy laws may not be as protective as in your place of residence. By providing your Personal Information to us, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Information to other countries for processing consistent with this Privacy Policy, as well as to subsequent transfers of such information consistent with the other terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Marketing Communications

We may send you email or other messages about us or our products and services. By the Privacy Policy or using the Services, you affirmatively consent to receive such commercial messages. You can ask to have your Personal Information removed from our mailing list and stop receiving future communication from us by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at support@apester.com. You will also be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from commercial messages in any such email or other message we send. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages, relating either to your account or to your transactions using the Services without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them unless you cancel your account.

## User’s Rights

User may at any time request information from Apester regarding his Personal Information stored at Apester, its origin, recipients or categories of recipients the data has been transferred to and the purpose of storage.  
Upon written request by User Apester will make all commercially reasonable efforts to delete any information provided to it, unless required otherwise for further execution of an agreement with a Customer or required by applicable laws. Apester cannot restore information that it has deleted.  
For executing any of these rights User may contact Apester by sending an email to privacy@apester.com or sending a paper letter to Apester’s Privacy Officer at the following address: Soncino 3 Tel Aviv 67216, P.O.box 57703, Israel. Facsimile copies can be sent to the following number: 153-3-6020065, however we do encourage you to reach out via email which is checked more often.

## Changes

Apester may update this Privacy Policy from time to time – we encourage you to review it periodically. We reserve the right to modify this policy. If required under applicable law, we will provide you with written notice of our changes. We will not make changes that have a material retroactive effect unless we are legally required to do so. Your continued use of the Services constitutes your acceptance of the amended policy. The amended policy supersede all previous versions, notices or statements of or about the policy.

## Comments and Questions / Contact Information

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@apester.com.
